[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "For her services to fashion, Vivienne Westwood was awarded what order of chivalry in 1992?", "correct_answer": "Officer of the Order of the British Empire", "incorrect_answers": ["Order of the Holy Sepulchre", "Dame Grand Cross of the British Empire", "Dame Commander of the British Empire"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What U.S. state is nicknamed Land of Infinite Variety?", "correct_answer": "South Dakota", "incorrect_answers": ["South Carolina", "Florida", "Delaware"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "How many pecks are in 8 bushels?", "correct_answer": "32", "incorrect_answers": ["16", "36", "24"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What was the name of the wagon cook in the western series Rawhide?", "correct_answer": "Wishbone", "incorrect_answers": ["Pete", "Rowdy", "Charley Grub"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Meryl Streep played the wife of Sam Bowden in Cape Fear.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "A cats sense of hearing is much more sensitive than that of a human or a dog.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the least common multiple (LCM) of 5, 6, and 10?", "correct_answer": "30", "incorrect_answers": ["20", "10", "15"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which part of the brain, located inside the temporal lobe, is associated with memory formation?", "correct_answer": "hippocampus", "incorrect_answers": ["subthalamus", "amygladala", "hypothalamus"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "A piece of wood floating on the ocean has what kind of buoyancy?", "correct_answer": "Positive buoyancy", "incorrect_answers": ["None of these", "Neutral buoyancy", "Negative buoyancy"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What does sneezing while talking mean according to Russian superstition?", "correct_answer": "The person is telling the truth.", "incorrect_answers": ["They will be healthy and will live long.", "The sneezing person is lying.", "The sneezing person will receive money soon."]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This rare, slow burning, strong-tasting tobacco is used as a component of many blended pipe tobaccos, but is too strong to be smoked pure.", "correct_answer": "Perique", "incorrect_answers": ["Havana", "Virginia", "Cavendish"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This novel told the story of two families, the Hamiltons and the Trasks, living in the Salinas Valley in California.  It is loosely based on Biblical stories.", "correct_answer": "East of Eden", "incorrect_answers": ["My Brothers Keeper", "The Tree of Life", "The Caine Mutiny"]}]